let MCQS = [
  {
  question: "JavaScript is which type of language?",
  choice1: "Object Oriented",
  choice2: "Object Based",
  choice3: "Procedural",
  choice4: "None",
  answer:0
},
{
  question: "Arrays in JavaScript are defined by which of the following statements?" ,
  choice1:"It is an ordered list of values" ,
  choice2:"It is an ordered list of objects" ,
  choice3: "It is an ordered list of string",
  choice4: "It is an ordered list of functions",
  answer:0
},
{
  question:"Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?" ,
  choice1:"<pre>" ,
  choice2: "<a>",
  choice3: "<b>",
  choice4: "<br>" ,
  answer:2
},
{
  question:" <input> is -" ,
  choice1: "a format tag.",
  choice2: "an empty tag.",
  choice3: "All of the above",
  choice4:"None of the above" ,
  answer:0
},
{
  question:"Which of the following tag is used to define options in a drop-down selection list?" ,
  choice1: "<select>",
  choice2: "<list>",
  choice3: "<dropdown>",
  choice4:"<option>" ,
  answer:3
},
{
  question:"Which of the following tag is used to add rows in the table?" ,
  choice1: "<td> and </td>",
  choice2: "<th> and </th>",
  choice3: "<tr> and </tr>",
  choice4: "None of the above",
  answer:2
},
{
  question:"CSS stands for -" ,
  choice1: "Cascade style sheets",
  choice2:"Color and style sheets" ,
  choice3:"Cascading style sheets" ,
  choice4:"None of the above" ,
  answer:3
},
{
  question:"The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -" ,
  choice1:"bgcolor" ,
  choice2: "color",
  choice3: "background-color",
  choice4:"All of the above" ,
  answer:2
},
{
  question:"Which of the following is the correct syntax to display the hyperlinks without any underline?" ,
  choice1:"a {text-decoration : underline;}" ,
  choice2:"a {decoration : no-underline;}" ,
  choice3: "a {text-decoration : none;}",
  choice4: "None of the above",
  answer:2
},
{
  question:" Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property for the padding properties?" ,
  choice1:"padding-left" ,
  choice2:"padding-right" ,
  choice3: "padding",
  choice4:"All of the above" ,
  answer:2
}];

